Joanna Jurasz

Junior Fullstack Developer



Personal Info

Email

joanna.jurasz21@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/joanna-jurasz/

Phone

+48 697 170 317

GitHub

https://github.com/JJonka

Website

https://jjurasz.com/

Skills

 JavaScript
 ★★★★★

 CSS
 ★★★★★

 Git
 ★★★★★

 HTML
 ★★★★

 Jest
 ★★★★

 MongoDB
 ★★★★

 Prisma
 ★★★★

 React
 ★★★★

 Storybook
 ★★★★

 Typescript
 ★★★★★

 Express
 ★★★★★

I am a very motivated junior fullstack developer. I am experienced in both frontend and backend technologies. At this point, my biggest challenge was to create a database for a building depot catalog page. Now, my goal is to find a job where I could improve my skills by working on interesting projects. I am easy to work with, reliable, and ready for challenges.

Work History

2023-11 - present

Fullstack Developer

KAR HUD Software Development, Kraków

My responsibilites involve:

- · creating scalable and responsive web application,
- writing unit tests, using React Testing Library and Jest,
- · debugging code with browser/text editor debugger,
- · doing code review,
- · planning and consulting creation of components with client,
- cooperation with other developers in creating generic components library,
- · using Storybook,
- · using version control system git,
- · work planning and time management using Jira,
- · making operations on databases,
- · creating and managing application's server.

Currently, I am mainly focused on creating a web application for a building depot. The project requires creating a database with the current product list, which will be updated every time something is changed or removed from the original file. For this job, I have chosen technologies like MongoDB, Express.js, React and Vite.

Internship

2023-04 - 2023-11

Application for estate agents

The project involved working with a team of two seniors and few juniors to create real estate agents manager. The application includes features like list of clients, that can be match with estates in database based on preferences they have. It also allows to create and manage list of meeting.

Technology used:

- React,
- Typescript,
- Nextjs,
- · Styled components,
- Graphql,
- · Nest,
- · Prisma,
- · Docker,
- Material-UI.

My responsibilities involved implementation of a form for adding new meetings. This project allowed me to learn and practice team work using technologies like Github and Jira.

Languages

English - B2

2022-06 *D-KART*

geodesy-web-page.vercel.app

Link to the repository: https://github.com/FutureInventor/GeodesyWebPage

The project involved working with a small team (two juniors, one senior) to create business homepage for a geodesic company. My responsibilities included creating responsive views based on prepaired earlier mock-ups and performing a code review.

The technology used:

HTML,

CSS,

VanillaJS.

Jira,

Git.

Projects

2023-09

My portfolio site

- 2023-10

https://jjurasz.com/

Technologies used:

- · React,
- · Typescript,
- HTML,
- · CSS Modules,
- · Vite.

2020-10

- 2021-06

Creating a hemoglobin measuring device using the open-source platform Arduino and 3D printing technology

This project was a part of my master's thesis. I was working with the open-source electronic platform Arduino and 3D printing to create small and mobile POCT (Point of Care Testing) device, allowing for hemoglobin concentration measurement in capillary blood.

My work included:

- designing the optical system and all of the device case using Tinkercad,
- printing designed parts using 3D printer,
- assembling the electronic system consisting of: light source, light sensor,
 LCD display and Arduino Mega 2560 microcontroller board,
- developing software, which allowed making hemoglobin measurements in the sample based on two reference measurements, using the programming tools provided by Arduino.

Education

2016-09

Medical Analytics, Master's degree

- 2021-07

Jagiellonian University Medical College, Kraków

Hobby/Interest

My favourite thing to do is assembling furniture, using hammer, screwdrivers and etc. I think that the main reason why I enjoyed working on my master's thesis was that I was building something. In my spare time I like to go swimming or hiking with my friends.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.